<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Container version="2">
  <Name>CommercialBreaker</Name>
  <Category>MediaServer: Tools:</Category>
  <Overview>Relive Toonami with a custom marathon generator that slices anime, injects ads, and builds a full channel. Because your anime deserves commercial breaks.</Overview>
  <Project>https://github.com/theweebcoders/CommercialBreaker</Project>
  <Support>https://discord.gg/S7NcUdhKRD</Support>
  <Description>
    &lt;h3&gt;CommercialBreaker &amp; Toonami Tools: Because Your Anime Deserves Commercial Breaks&lt;/h3&gt;

    Hey there, space cowboy. Remember those long Toonami nights filled with anime and the oddly comforting interruption of commercials? Ever thought your sleek, ad-free Plex server felt a little too... smooth? Well, we've got the fix for you, because here, we're mixing the future with a splash of the past.

    Welcome aboard the Absolution, where we're on a mission to boldly put the commercials back into your favorite anime. Why? Because we can. Because it's a kind of nostalgia that just feels right.

    We've got two Python apps in our hyperdrive: CommercialBreaker and Toonami Tools. They'll slice up your anime and make room for those memory-ridden ads you secretly miss. Want your Plex server to feel like a marathon Toonami night? We got you. Got DizqueTV all set up? Even better. You one of those fancy new tunarr users? We've got you covered too.

    So, who's the bigger otaku here? The person adding commercials back into their anime, or the mad scientist who spent a year and six months in the coding mines to make it happen? No matter, we're all in this giant robot together.

    Until next time, stay gold.

    &lt;h4&gt;What it does&lt;/h4&gt;

    Toonami Tools and CommercialBreaker automate a continuous Toonami marathon.

    Here's how it works:
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Provide a directory with multi-lineup bumps, transitional bumps, and shows.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;The marathon starts with a lineup bump, like "Toonami 2.0: Now Bleach, Next Naruto, Later One Piece."&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;"Bleach" airs, with transitional bumps for commercials. AKA Bleach will be right back &amp; Now more bleach&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;After "Bleach," "Naruto" airs with its commercial transitions.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;The tools then select the next lineup bump starting with "One Piece," such as "Toonami 2.0: Now One Piece, Next Blue Exorcist, Later Black Lagoon."&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;This pattern continues, using the end of one bump to determine the start of the next.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;

    The result is an unbroken Toonami marathon, where multi-lineup bumps set the sequence and transitions connect each lineup smoothly.

    The brilliance of these tools lies in their ability to create an unbroken Toonami marathon, using the multi-lineup bumps to define the sequence, and seamlessly connecting the end of one lineup to the beginning of another.

    ☕ Support your local mad scientist: &lt;a href="https://www.buymeacoffee.com/tim000x3"&gt;Buy Me A Coffee&lt;/a&gt;

    Full README and lore: &lt;a href="https://github.com/theweebcoders/CommercialBreaker"&gt;GitHub Repo&lt;/a&gt;

    Need help? Join the resistance: &lt;a href="https://discord.gg/S7NcUdhKRD"&gt;Discord&lt;/a&gt;
  </Description>
  <Registry>https://hub.docker.com/r/tim000x3/commercial-breaker</Registry>
  <Repository>tim000x3/commercial-breaker</Repository>
  <BindTime>true</BindTime>
  <WebUI>http://[IP]:[PORT:8081]</WebUI>
  <Icon>https://avatars.githubusercontent.com/u/172365950?s=400&u=7a2a1b390dff7240cfc5a662414c90d19eef7217&v=4</Icon>
  <ExtraParams></ExtraParams>

  <Network>bridge</Network>
  <Networking>
    <Mode>bridge</Mode>
    <Publish>
      <Port>
        <HostPort>8081</HostPort>
        <ContainerPort>8081</ContainerPort>
        <Protocol>tcp</Protocol>
      </Port>
    </Publish>
  </Networking>

  <Data>
    <Volume>
      <HostDir>/mnt/user/media/anime</HostDir>
      <ContainerDir>/app/anime</ContainerDir>
      <Mode>rw</Mode>
    </Volume>
    <Volume>
      <HostDir>/mnt/user/media/bumps</HostDir>
      <ContainerDir>/app/bump</ContainerDir>
      <Mode>rw</Mode>
    </Volume>
    <Volume>
      <HostDir>/mnt/user/media/special_bumps</HostDir>
      <ContainerDir>/app/special_bump</ContainerDir>
      <Mode>rw</Mode>
    </Volume>
    <Volume>
      <HostDir>/mnt/user/appdata/commercialbreaker/working</HostDir>
      <ContainerDir>/app/working</ContainerDir>
      <Mode>rw</Mode>
    </Volume>
  </Data>
</Container>